RPA / uiPath

Bot store, 
selenium and uipath (rpa)
why need agent in .net. NuGet is an extension of Microsoft visual studio which provides interface for managing third-party libraries for .NET projects. NuGet uses file type Nupkg.


about rpa/uipath from wiki
RPA is robotic process automation used for business process automation based on the notion of software robots or AI workers.
there is a concept of software bot who will do different tasks using keyboard and mouse. If you take the analogy of robot, they have hand to execute tasks, software bots have mouse and keyboard. Instructions to bot is given using xaml or nupkg files. These bots has their own virtual environment. They dont need physical desktop. 


selenium is designed only for web application testing. it cant interact with multiple application, take output from one application and feed the same to other application as input. RPA does that. RPA is next level of existing automation tools. You can do all things using UIPath which can be done by Selenium but vice versa is not passible. 

UI path licensing: https://robot.uipath.com/docs/about-licensing#

UI path designer: you can create flowchart or sequence. A workflow can contain other workflow or sequence. Flowchart can have decisions.

Different activities in UI path:
Start, Assign (to assign values to variables), Message box,
Decision, if,  
UIPath credential:
username: akhilesh4u3
password: Pass@1002

Directory.GetFiles(selectedFolder)
new Random().Next(0,100)
-----
configuring bot macine:

netsh http add urlacl url=http://+:8080/ user=corp\q4465


======
to write in notepad

-open application 
-attach window
 -type into
-close application


==============
project QK Controller
-prerequisite: 
.NET > 4.5.2


update C:\Users\q4465\workspace5\QkClient\DemoServiceHost\bin\Debug\QKClientHost.exe.config in QKClient project-> update the server host address which http://localhost:8081/ for QKController.

uirobot path: C:\Program Files (x86)\UiPath\Studio

To run a xaml file from command line:

c:\Program Files (x86)\UiPath\Studio>UiRobot.exe -file "C:\Users\q4465\Documents\UiPath\intro\guessNumber.xaml"